thetypingcat.com 2016-05-07

# Privacy Policy - The Typing Cat

## Privacy Policy

### Does application collect information about you?

Yes, we collect some information from you when you register on our site or fill out a from. However, you can use this website anonymously.

The most important fact is we will not sell your private data that we collect on our site to any business partner, without your permission.

### Why we gather information from you?

Any of information we gather may be used in some of listed below ways: 

  * Tailoring a website to improve our service.
  * Personalize your experience to suit your individual needs.

### Is my personal data secure?

We provide reasonable administrative, technical security measures in place to protect your personal information. However, despite of any our efforts, no security sytems are 100% effective so we cannot warrant the security of your personal information.

### What are cookies? Why do we use them?

A cookie, also known as browser/web cookie, is a small piece of data sent from a website and stored on a user's computer while the user is browsing web. We use them to identify you and let you access your account data.

### Third party links/vendors/ads

This web site contains links to other web sites and third party Ads. Please note that when you click on one of these links you are redirected to another web site on which privacy policy may differ from ours so please read it. As well advertisement vendors can use cookies to serve their ads. This Privacy Policy covers the usage of cookies by The Typing Cat and does not cover the usage of cookies by any third party vendors. 

### Do we comply with COPPA?

No, this website is not directed to children under 13.

### Terms of Service

Please also read our Terms of Service.

### How can I contact The Typing Cat with questions or concerns?

Please feel free to email us at info@thetypingcat.com.

### Will this website privacy policy change in future?

Occasionally, we may change or update our privacy policy here.

Last Updated: March 1, 2014
